Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/thiendang-17191a112 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Front-end Development Spring Boot

Thien Dang

Senior Software Engineering at Evolable Asia CO., LTD. Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Java Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Spring Boot, Hibernate, Mac, Tortoise SVN, and Java. Strong engineering professional with a Good focused in Computer Software Technology/Technician from FPT university.

Experience

Evolable Asia CO., LTD.
Senior Software Engineering
December 2016 - Present (4 years 11 months)
ha noi

Product project for Japan company

Framgia Inc.

Java Software Engineer
July 2016 - July 2017 (1 year 1 month)

ha noi

Skypeld: shandangit

FPT Software

Deverlop

January 2014 - August 2016 (2 years 8 months)

Ha noi

Skype: shandangit

Education

FPT university

Good, Computer Software Technology/Technician · (2010 - 2014)

Activity

10/27/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)